Mail received
Mashiro...
Mashiro Moritaka
We did it
First chapter of PCP got 1st place!
Does that get us a bit closer to our dream?
We did it!
PCP's first chapter got 1st place in the rankings!
First chapter of PCP got 1st place!
Does that get us a bit closer to our dream?
We'll be fine.
We're definitely getting closer to our dream.
ano ne moshimo ima sugu ni kimi no moto he to
Hey, if I could go to where you are right now
ikeru naraba kono koe ga nakunattemo ii ya
then I could accept losing my voice
mezasu basho ga amari ni mo tooku
The goals I've set myself seem impossible to reach,
boku wa mou michi ni mayoisou da
and I feel lost on my path
kowareta jishaku wo ate ni shiteru n da
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in another's shadow
dareka no kage ni kakurete sa
nanika wo te ni ireru tame nanika wo tebanasu nante koto wo
If we keep letting go of some things in order to find something else,
tsuzukete mo kitto bokura wa otona ni wa narenai
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
narenai
Never
Tenacity and Determination
Are we clear?
+Natural will be the best manga in Jack.
No, in all of Japan.
Losing to PCP is out of the question!
I-It'll be okay.
We've got an anime starting this April, after all.
Oh, right.
I was given this to show you.
Candidates for the role of Mimiya Sayano, who appears starting in episode 16.
Since there are four applicants, they wanted the opinion of the authors.
I'll get Niizuma's opinion the next time we meet.
And you—
Azuki Miho...
We were classmates in my third year of middle school.
What, really?
What a coincidence.
Azuki Miho
aaaa
Filmography:
Birthday:
Data:
POB:
5/11/1993
height 162cm, weight 44kg
Saitama, currently lives in Tokyo
She's Mashiro's girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
She visited him several times when he was in the hospital.
Azuki Miho
Azuki Miho.
Mashiro Moritaka
Mashiro Moritaka.
Takagi Akito
Takagi Akito.
Ashirogi Mutou
Ashirogi Mutou!
The first chapter is number one!
You're off to a great start!
Yeah. Now we have to keep
working hard to maintain a high rank.
For that, we have to overcome the weak points of the characters!
But is making Mai athletic overdoing it?
She's a heroine. That much is expected.
Right, right.
Who is it?
It's Miura.
Oh, Mashiro?
As I recall, Azuki Miho went to middle school with you, and she's your...
Uh, yes.
Just how amazing is your middle school?
There's Ashirogi and Akina, and Azuki Miho is a voice actress...
She's pretty accomplished too. I was surprised.
Um, why are we talking about Azuki Miho?
Because she's an applicant for the role of
Mimiya Sayano, the heroine of +Natural.
An applicant for the role of Sayano?!
What, you didn't know?
The audition is next Saturday.
I'm rooting for her.
See ya.
Azuki in Natural...
Why?
Saikou.
What was that all about?
Were you talking about Miho?
Yeah.
Why did Miura call about Azuki?
He said that Azuki is an applicant for the role of Sayano.
"Sayano?"
This girl.
Natural's heroine.
Isn't this Iwase and Niizuma's manga?!
He said the audition's next Saturday.
So that's why he...
Yeah. He's their editor, after all.
He just called to say how amazing it is that she's a voice actress.
Wh-Why is Miho auditioning for that character?
She's supposed to play the role of
Annojo Mai when PCP becomes an anime!
Sayano gets introduced late,
but there are no other female characters that stand out.
Given how the events unfold, she's sure to become the main heroine.
What?
Miho's going to be the heroine for
Ashirogi Mutou. She can't be anyone else's!
Especially not for the manga created by your rivals, Iwase and Niizuma!
No way!
Mashiro, stop her!
No.
The bigger the role, the better for her career.
But...
What happened to your dream of getting married
after Miho stars in the anime adaptation of your manga?
A job is a job.
Marriage comes after we do our best at manga and voice acting, respectively.
Right now, Iwase and Eiji are doing better than us with Natural.
That's just how it s.
What are you saying? Don't you think this is wrong?!
That's messed up—
Kaya.
What?
It's none of your business.
How mean.
I just want what's best for everyone...
I understand how you feel, but it's not our place to say anything.
But...
You can't say things like that in front of Saikou.
I don't think he really wants her to do it, either.
But he won't stop her from doing work that she's chosen to do.
Why not?
He's stubborn!
Stubborn, huh? I can see that.
He's not very honest when it comes to things like this.
Neither is Azuki.
For sure.
But why did she audition for Sayano?
You'd think she'd say, "I can't be in an anime by Mashiro's rival!"
But she's not that type of girl.
She'd just say "It's a job, so I have to do my best."
It's her job offer, so it's up to her to decide.
Let's go to her house tomorrow.
O-Okay.
Welcome, you two!
It's been a while.
Sorry for coming on such short notice.
It's fine. I have so much to ask you!
Come on, come in.
Ask us?
I see.
But how did you hear about this?
We happened to hear it from Natural's editor.
Why are you auditioning?
My manager sent in the application on his own...
I see. And you passed.
Yeah.
When's the audition?
This Saturday...
at 1 PM.
Where?
A studio near Shibuya.
What will you do?
Huh?
You shouldn't do it!
It'd be horrible if you pass!
If you land the role of Sayano,
what will you do when our work becomes an anime?
That would make you the heroine in two Jack productions.
No matter how hard Mashiro and I push for you,
they'll just say "She's already doing Natural."
Mashiro said that?
Mashiro's the same as ever. He's keeps insisting
that it's up to you to decide since it's your job.
I see.
That's just how he is.
I know how he feels, but I don't want you to do this.
Takagi?
There's no guarantee that our manga will become an anime anytime soon,
but you'll be the heroine when it does.
Natural's not the only anime out there!
You shouldn't do something that
takes you further away from your dream!
Don't be so stubborn. Be honest with yourself!
Kaya...
If you say you won't go to the audition, Mashiro will definitely be happy!
That's right.
If you say that, Saikou will be relieved.
If he told you not to go, you'd be happy, right?
That's right!
The two of you are too stubborn.
In any case, you should at least decide to avoid major roles
in any Jack anime adaptation from here on out!
Well, like Saikou says, it's your
work, so it's up to you to decide.
But I don't want you to accept the role just because Mashiro didn't stop you.
I understand.
I'll text him today and ask.
Huh? But you know exactly what he'll say!
Kaya, we've done all we can.
The rest is for Azuki and Saikou to decide.
Let's go.
But we didn't get anywhere!
Come on.
Akito!
See you later, Azuki!
Azuki voicing Sayano...
Damn it!
New mail
Azuki Miho
Azuki!
aaaaaaaaaa
Azuki Miho
Good evening
Are we stubborn?
Stubborn, huh?
Mail received
aaaaaaaaaa
Mashiro Moritaka
Re: Good evening
I dunno.
Mashiro
All right! First page, done!
Let's keep up the good work!
Kaya, can't you be a bit quieter?
Huh? Why?
I have to keep everyone's spirits up!
You're making it hard for them to concentrate.
Mashiro.
Yes?
This panel on the third page...
In this rough sketch of the scenery, the
perspective on the characters is a bit off.
Let me see.
You're right.
I'll fix it right away.
Moriya's the same as ever.
No.
I think something's off this week too.
Huh?
I can fix the mistakes I'm finding,
but there are more than usual this week.
R-Really?
Yes.
I just hope we can fix them all before we have to turn in the manuscript tomorrow.
PCP came in 2nd.
Crow was 3rd, and Natural was 5th.
All right!
I'll come over at 6 to pick up the manuscript.
Okay!
And the Natural anime will start in a month.
He told us not to get comfortable!
We're safe if our second chapter is in 2nd place.
It's a good response from the readers.
It is, but...
Azuki voicing Sayano in Natural...
Am I really okay with that?
Start
The audition is tomorrow.
Saikou...
Oh, that's great.
Let's keep it up.
You already made copies.
Ah... I wasted a sheet of paper.
I told Azuki that she shouldn't go to the
audition just because you won't stop her.
Wh-Why?
I feel bad for butting in, but...
No.
Thanks...
The story's good, as usual.
But Mashiro, what's wrong?
I can't feel your usual delicacy in the art.
This won't—
Hattori!
Mashiro!
I'm sorry. Is it still possible to make revisions?
I'd like to say "okay", but I've got a meeting in three hours.
It's only a few pages, so I'll just take it as is.
Sorry!
I'll fix it in two hours, so please give me some time!
Saikou!
I'll help with anything. Tell me what to do.
No.
You created a perfect story.
So it's my job to perfect the art.
If I can't do that, I can't call myself a pro!
Saikou...
Azuki is working hard as a voice actress for her own sake.
aaaaaaaaaa
Azuki Miho
Good evening
Are we stubborn?
It's not about being stubborn.
Because I care about her, respect her, and trust her,
I won't stop her if she doesn't withdraw from the audition.
But like Shuujin said, maybe it isn't
right to push the decision all onto her.
aaaaaaaaaa
Mashiro Moritaka
Re: Good evening
I dunno.
Mashiro...
That line was great!
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
How about it, Niizuma? Did
anyone's voice catch your attention?
Difficult...
They were all good.
It's difficult to make a distinction.
Then, Azuki Miho—
But.
I think it's best to give up on Azuki Miho.
What? She's no good?
Right. Because she's Mashiro's girlfriend.
If she appears in our work,
I don't think Mashiro and Takagi will be happy about it.
Really?
But she is a voice actress...
Well, come tomorrow, don't say anything about refusing her because of that.
I know.
Well then, I'll see you at the audition tomorrow.
Good luck, Miho.
I'm off, then.
Take care.
Miho.
This may not be any of my business, but when you're in doubt, be true to your feelings.
People won't like you if you're stubborn!
Stubborn...
March
Day
Sat
Sun
Mon
Tues
Manuscript UP
The audition's today.
Yeah.
I wonder what Miho's doing...
Just be quiet and watch over them.
But...
It was supposed to start at 1 PM.
Really? I'm so happy!
I'll do my best!
I'll become a voice actress and star in your anime!
It's wonderful!
I'll be waiting.
I'll always be waiting.
Mashiro, let's do our best.
I believe in you.
Let's make our dream come true.
Hachihata Studio
Oh! We're here!
But we're a bit early.
LET'S AUDITION!
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Miura, what floor is it on?
Uh, let's see... the second floor.
Roger!
It's been a while.
Ashirogi Mutou.
What does that pen name mean?
"A" from Azuki, "shiro" from Mashiro,
"gi" from Takagi,
and "Mutou" from "to grant dreams."
It means that their work will become an anime, and I will play the heroine.
That is our dream!
Oh! That's a fantastic dream!
They made a manga based on that frivolous dream?!
That is why I came here today to turn down the role.
Don't be ridiculous!
After hearing that story, I'm absolutely determined to use you.
I'll make Sayano into the best heroine possible.
I won't allow you to turn it down because of your love life.
It'll be a huge problem for you if you refuse.
I don't care.
Were women always this scary?
Yes, they are.
Mashiro!
Let's go!
Where?
We're getting out of here!
O-Okay!
Stop!
Don't think you can get away with this—
You're so cool, Mashiro!
Leave it to me!
On my authority, I will reject her!
I won't let anyone complain about it!
Thanks, Niizuma!
Thank you!
Love, love!
Love will wiener!
I sure did it this time.
But I'm happy.
Even though I interfered with your work?
I was about to refuse the role, though.
We made the same decision.
We were on the exact same wavelength, weren't we?
And... you held my hand.
Ah, sorry! This is, err, um...
Sorry for letting go.
You're quite reliable today, Mashiro.
Are you saying I'm usually not?
Yeah. Aside from manga, there are parts of you that are a bit iffy.
And you're stubborn.
That goes for both of us.
We're so stubborn and yet we can't even keep a promise.
Just how many times have we seen
each other after we promised not to?
It was an emergency.
Unfortunately, life is like that.
You're disappointed, Mashiro?
Yeah. I didn't intend to hold hands
with you until our dream came true.
You really are stubborn.
I won't forgive her!
Miura!
We're having a meeting right after this audition.
Understood?
Y-Yes!
Let's start the auditions now!
After Shinjuku, I take the Saikyo line.
You take the Chuo line, right?
Yes.
We haven't even been together five minutes...
Can I go with you to Yakusa?
B-But I have to make a clean copy of the name!
I'll only stay with you until we get to Yakusa.
Then I'll go home.
For some reason, Azuki's being pretty bold today...
Is it because we're holding hands?
All right! I won't let go of your hand until we reach Yakusa!
You really are reliable today, Mashiro.
R-Really?
Nakamuramachi
Kitayakusa
Minamiyakusa
Funado
This reminds me of when we were in the hospital.
We don't talk much when we're together.
Yeah.
But I'm happy.
Next stop is Minamiyakusa. Minamiyakusa.
It's the next stop.
40 minutes went by so quickly.
Time always passes quickly when you are happy.
Minamiyakusa
Nakamuramachi
Kitayakusa
Well, then..
Mashiro.
The next time we meet...
Let's kiss.
What's wrong with you, Azuki?
Is it because we held hands?!
Even so, should we be kissing just like that?!
That's not like you!
Because the next time we meet... our dream will have come true!
Until our dream comes true...
Azuki is Azuki, after all.
That face is telling me they did more than see each other.
Huh? He's just happy because she
didn't go through with the audition.
I'm telling you, something happened!
Like what?
You don't think...
I'm going to ask him!
I-Idiot! Don't!
Mashiro!
Something good happened between you and Miho, right?
It's written all over your face!
On my face? No way!
What did you do?
Confess!
Nothing, really.
No way!
You at least kissed, right?
Your face gives it away!
Kiss? No, we didn't!
We really didn't!
Just spill it, already!
Hands?
That's all?
You just held hands?!
That's just like you two.
Actually, that's great progress!
Are you two in grade school, or something?!
Shut up.
We can do what we want.
Azuki Miho!
I won't forgive her!
I'll make her regret turning down the role!
I'll destroy her career as a voice actress!
I'll drag Ashirogi Mutou down with her!
I don't care what it takes! Give me any ideas you have!
Mashiro and Miho aren't messing around.
They're giving it their all.
Are you on their side?
Come to think of it, PCP is a manga that you helped create.
I'm Natural's editor!
I want to help you more than anyone else!
It's true.
Besides, authors should compete
against each other with their works.
That's the only way I can help you.
Then come up with an idea for the next chapter!
Hattori gave me one after another!
Come on!
Right...
Um... where did we leave off last time?
You can't even remember that?
I'm sorry!
PCP's third chapter came in 5th place.
Natural is...
in 4th, right above PCP.
I wonder if Akina will calm down a bit when she hears this.
Hattori, what's wrong?
PCP's third chapter did well, didn't it?
You have to hurry and tell Ashirogi!
Yeah, you're right.
The third chapter is in 5th.
Normally, this would be considered great, but...
They have six months.
We'll see how it goes until their 25th chapter.
If their ratings are too low by their seventh chapter, I won't hesitate to cancel it.
And if they can't compete against Crow and Natural by their 25th chapter,
I'll cancel it then and there.
This just isn't good enough.
At the very least, we need to be even with +Natural within a half year.
We can't afford to drop any lower than this.
Popular series! Ashirogi Mutou
PCP - Perfect Crime Party
I have to do something!
Popular series! Ashirogi Mutou
PCP - Perfect Crime Party
mogakinagara saikou no yume wo
The times when I fight and struggle and dream
katachi ni suru kono shunkan ga suki sa
of all the things I want in life is the best
tatakau you na te wo tsunagu you na
That's when I feel the bond between us and our strength to fight
kankaku ga shigekiteni da ne
Our view of the world overlaps and stimulates us
kousa shite
dakara motto migakou jibun rashiku arou
Let us polish ourselves, be more like how we should be
tsuzuita michi ni aru hazu
The future can be found on the path we walk
mirai wa
shinzuru mono ga chigau nakamatachi
My comrades believe in different things than me
Rival...and Friend!
butsukariau Pride
Our pride clashes
yuzurenai kore kara mo kokoro no mama susumou yo
I can't give up on it, I have to do what my heart commands me to do
junbi wa dekita
I'm ready
ikki ni kakeagaru tame no
I've got the unbending pride
akiramenai Pride
to run to the top now
hisshi nanda yo suki dakara suki wo mune ni susumu n da
This is my only choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
donna ashita ga matteru ka shiranai
I don't know what tomorrow will be like
asu mo
But I know that tomorrow, again,
bokura wa
girigiri
ganbatteru darou
we will do our best to get by
Next Time
Preview
Our new serialization has finally started up,
but we've been given some strict conditions!
Can we overcome them, even while our rivals work against us?
Next time: Every Night and Unite.
Every Night and
Unite
Only hard work can connect our dreams!