Man, this week's name is good too.
Your enthusiasm really shines through.
Never mind that.
How did I do in the rankings this week?
Crow came in 1st again.
Is that so?
I'll keep working hard and come in 1st next week too.
yu
me
Dreams, dreams, dreams, dreams
As soon as I reach my goals, it all falls through again
So why do I run...
...and search in spite of that?
atta
We met after such a long time
watta?"
"Has the mood changed for us?"
So much time has passed
"It seemed like more fun back then"
We've lost so much
I already know that, though
Don't stop screaming, don't stop struggling
rou?
You've done enough for others
I still, still have something I haven't told you yet
Beyond each of my dreams lies yet another dream
Serialization and Prevention
Crow's been ranked 1st three weeks in a row.
Climax
of
the
Sky
Prison
saga!!
Climax
of
the
Sky
Prison
saga!!
Niizuma is incredible.
Yeah.
Catching up to him won't be as easy as we made it sound.
Apparently, Niizuma's been devoting a lot of time into revising his names lately.
Seriously?!
His names?!
Yeah. He's been working on them for days on end.
I wonder what happened.
Maybe he's trying to egg us on?
Well, knowing that Crow is ranked 1st does make me feel more motivated...
See?
It's Niizuma's way of lighting a fire under us!
Yeah!
We've gotta surpass him in the rankings and return the favor!
Here's Crow and Natural's manuscripts.
Thank you!
Nothing has changed this week, either.
Was I worrying too much?
It's a seven year old promise, after all.
Um, Niizuma, congrats on Crow coming in 1st.
Thank you.
Think you can do something about Natural too?
I haven't been slacking on the art. What's the problem?
There's nothing wrong with the art.
But it's dropped in the rankings ever since the anime ended,
and this week it's 10th.
I know you're doing the art for both, but...
It's because the story for Natural isn't interesting.
I'm not the story writer.
If you want it to be popular,
you and Akina have to make the story compelling.
R-Right.
Niizuma's got a point.
The latest chapters are pretty dull.
The story's turned into an endless repetition of
defeating bad guys, each one stronger than the last.
Yes, it's the same pattern over and over again.
You two sure don't pull any punches.
The story might improve if I'm allowed to make changes.
But I can only change so many things.
Akina has her pride, after all.
Yeah, no kidding.
Forming a relationship with her similar to what Ashirogi Mutou has won't be easy.
At least Natural's manga issues are still selling well...
Do you think Niizuma doesn't like the way Natural is dragging on?
Yeah.
It's certainly past its peak.
I'm finding it hard to breathe when it's just the two of us, Nakai.
It's like there's less oxygen in here than there should be.
It's not like I actually want to be your assistant.
That's no reason to let the quality of your art drop, Nakai.
It won't match unless I drop my
quality down to the level of your art.
I don't know
what your goal is,
but please
spare me!
Oxygen
Why do you insist on talking to me like we're buddies?
Aren't I top dog here?
I get the feeling you think pretty highly of yourself.
Believe me, I'd rather not speak to you like we're friends.
Why not?
Because things are going well
between you and Aoki, obviously!
Nakai! Are you telling me you haven't given up on her?!
Oh, I just got an idea! I think we can use it.
I did give up on her, but I can't help but feel jealous!
Do you have any idea how I feel, having to work with you?!
What I'd give to have a girlfriend...
Why don't you ask Yoshida-shi for advice?
Huh?
It's no secret that my relationship with Aoki
started by following advice from Yoshida-shi.
Really?!
Speak of the devil.
What?
Nakai? With a girl?
Impossible.
I know, right?
Not even you can help him, Yoshida-shi.
Wait a second! If I can make this work...
Do you really want a girlfriend?
O-Of course!
You'd be required to follow a diet plan that I would create for you.
However, that would lessen a
negative influence on Hiramaru,
namely the financial burden of
supporting your overeating habits.
Is that all you care about, Yoshida-shi?!
But it's true that no matter how much you eat, that feed—I mean, food,
is not a major source of negativity for Hiramaru at this point in time.
More important is the risk that you would succumb to obesity-related diseases.
Your skills as an assistant are practically wasted on Hiramaru.
Nakai.
If you truly intend to follow my teachings,
then I'll rise to the challenge of
transforming you into a Super Mangaka.
Super Mangaka?!
Yes! Like a manga Super Saiyan!
We'll turn you into a first rate manga
author in mind, manners, agility, and looks.
You'll be able to turn the head of any woman—Aoki included!
You already have the skills. I know you can do it!
Yoshida-shi! What are you saying?!
I'll give it a shot!
N-Not you too, Nakai!
All right!
Start by running 10 km, mornings and evenings!
Yes, sir!
No way!
Forgive me, Hiramaru.
This tough love is necessary to keep your negativity flowing.
And if I can corrupt Nakai at the same time, that'll be two birds with one stone.
Oh! This makes Crow's fourth consecutive week at 1st!
Crow is doing unbelievably well.
It's popularity is the real thing.
It's because he's making things exciting by having all the characters participate in a final battle.
PCP's in 3rd.
Road Racer GIRI's anime just started, and now the manga is ranked right below us.
Once Seigi no Mikata's drama adaptation starts, it should skyrocket to the top of the rankings!
Hey, Yuujirou.
What's up?
Ashirogi sends their thanks.
Huh?
Crow's top ranking gave them some motivation.
So that's it!
I-Is something wrong?
Remember what I told you?
About earning the right to end a manga?
Yes...
I was worried that Niizuma might be going for that,
but it looks like he only has Ashirogi's best interests in mind.
If that's why he's so set on being in
first, he'll never come out and say it.
You came in 1st again.
I see. That's good.
It's business as usual, then.
Also, Ashirogi wants you to know that Crow's top ranking has motivated them.
Ashirogi?
Yeah.
What are they thinking?
What do you mean? They just wanted to thank you.
I'll become a Super Mangaka!
Now
Open
Welcome!
Yuujirou, Crow is 1st again!
Editorial Department
Shounen Jack
Jack SQ
X Jack
Huh? But today's Thursday...
Wait, rankings are out today since the holiday break starts tomorrow, right?
That's right. I left them on top of your desk.
What God Gave Me is... 7th.
Thanks!
Never Reaching You is 5th.
All right! This is good for now.
First place for five weeks in a row!
GIRI's at 3rd. The anime must have bumped it up.
My time has finally come!
I'm Hattori Yuujirou, editor of the 1st and 3rd ranked manga!
Just make me a team leader already!
Refusing on the basis of my youth is old-fashioned!
He's so full of himself!
Hard to argue with the 1st and 3rd rankings, though.
I'm off to Fukuda's house!
All right! Seigi no Mikata is in 6th!
Miura, you don't have time to be rejoicing.
Do something about Natural.
Oh, right.
GIRI beat us in the rankings?
PCP placing 4th isn't so bad,
but it can't outrank a manga that has
an anime, let alone catch up to Niizuma.
I'll never stop living on the edge!
It feels like he's going so fast!
It's only episode 3 and it's already this exciting!
With this, the manga's rankings and issue sales are sure to go up!
Great timing.
You came in 3rd place this week!
We're finally in the top three!
Getting first place might not be just a dream, after all!
Well, there's quite a gap between you and Crow.
You've got your work cut out for you.
You sure look happy.
Since you're already editing both, you won't give a damn if GIRI passes Crow, will you?
That's not true!
I'd be thrilled if GIRI got the top spot!
Ideally, newer manga should surpass long-running ones.
But it'd be really hard to surpass Crow.
It's come in first place for the last five weeks.
Niizuma being so set on coming in 1st had me feeling anxious for a while.
Why's that?
Didn't Nonaka tell you?
Niizuma asked for the right to end a manga he
hates if he ever became the no. 1 author in Jack.
Huh?
Needless to say, I told him he couldn't do that.
But the Chief told him, "We'll talk about it if you still feel that way once you've become our magazine's main attraction."
So what was the manga Niizuma wanted to end?
I really wanna know!
I haven't asked him, you know.
But this was decided when he was serialized seven years ago.
Maybe the manga he wanted to end is already over.
Yeah... And at this point in time, it'd probably be Natural.
Why?
He said the story's boring and
follows the same pattern over and over.
Are you sure you should be telling us this?
It's okay. I know Niizuma won't bring that deal up again.
His fixation on being 1st is just to motivate Ashirogi.
Besides, he's matured during his years of being serialized.
Wow!
Crow's come in first place five weeks in a row!
The story's getting exciting with the introduction of an all-out war.
And then we have PCP, which will never get an anime.
Saikou, don't you think it's about time we started thinking about another manga?
An unorthodox battle story with a mainstream character...
I've drawn the all-important
mainstream character a few times.
Have a look.
Wow!
This is pretty cool!
This too!
No, they're not good enough. I don't want to compromise.
What's wrong, Niizuma? This is unexpected...
I spoke with someone at the reception desk.
I didn't hear anything about that.
I came to meet with the Chief Editor.
I received approval.
The Chief?
Could he be...
You're the only one left, Falcon!
You're damn good, Giri. I always knew you were!
You never cease to amaze me, Falcon.
That's a perfect line.
Our moves are in perfect harmony.
But such perfect driving isn't my...
Go!
All right, here it comes!
My killer move! Triangle...
Fly Cornering!
Yuujirou's here to pick up the manuscript.
Right in the middle of the anime, again.
Things were just getting good.
Only a madman would think of a move like that!
Sorry to keep you waiting. Now, let's go!
Can't you let us watch the anime in peace?
Didn't I tell you?
I always win!
Sorry.
What's your problem?
Some girl wouldn't give you the time of day or something?
That can't be it. He's usually all
smiles, even when he gets rejected.
Yuujirou, Crow and GIRI had good rankings this week.
Yeah.
With the way things are looking,
Crow will be 1st again.
And why do you look depressed about that?
What a downer.
I think I know...
Yuujirou, you must be upset over Master Niizuma.
"Upset" doesn't even begin to describe it.
I knew it!
What?
Master Niizuma brought up the right to end a manga he hates, didn't he?
What're you talking about?!
Got any proof?!
Wh-Where's your manuscript?!
Here.
Thanks.
Listen you better....
curb your imagination.
And don't spread any... strange rumors!
He's so easy to read.
I wonder which manga Master Niizuma wants the right to end.
Last week, Yuujirou said it'd probably be Natural.
Miura!
Are we having this meeting or what?
Huh? Oh, yeah...
The anime's over and the manga's ranking has plummeted.
That's why I told you to be careful.
Excuse me.
Hello?
It's Aoki.
Sorry, but I'm in a meeting right now.
I'll call back later, then.
On second thought, if you have
something to tell me, you can say it now.
Okay...
A gathering at Fukuda's place?
Um, I'm not part of the so-called Team Fukuda.
But it's to discuss the possibility of Niizuma ending Natural...
I understand.
6 PM, right?
We don't even know if Niizuma's
actually been given the right to do this.
That's true.
But it's also true that Niizuma showed up at the editing department on Monday and spoke to the Chief Editor.
I heard this from Yoshida-shi.
Since they spoke in a separate room,
even Yoshida-shi, a team leader,
doesn't know what they talked about.
In other words, only Niizuma's editor, Yuujirou, knows.
And you know how Yuujirou's been acting.
It does seem likely that he was
granted the right to end a manga.
And that would be Natural?
No, maybe it's Never Reaching You!
Hiramaru, that's not something you should be happy about!
I still find it hard to believe that they'd give him that right just because he came in 1st a few times.
And the idea that he'd choose to end Natural is just speculation.
Yeah. It's partly his manga, after all.
Nothing can come from discussing this here!
I'm going to ask him directly .
So it's true that you asked for the right to end a manga you hate?
Yes.
And did you get it?
They'd never give him the right do something like that.
But they did.
With some conditions.
Conditions?
I have to get first place ten weeks in a row.
So I only need to come in first place for five more weeks!
I'll definitely get 1st in the next five weeks and end a manga.
Ten weeks in a row...
He came in first with a large lead in this week's initial ranking.
That means he actually has only four more weeks to go.
Tell us what manga you want to end!
Is it mine?
It is, isn't it?
The one I want to end...
is Crow!
Crow?
Hiramaru?
I knew it!
Wasn't it supposed to be a manga you hate?
I do hate it.
You do?
I hate not being able to end something in the way that I want.
I know that the editing department
doesn't want to end a popular manga.
The magazine is trying to make a profit, and I understand that.
But before I started drawing, I made a resolution.
I resolved to end my manga when I want to: at the
height of its popularity, in the coolest way possible.
It looks like I'll be able to do that, and I couldn't be happier.
The Chief wanted me to continue the manga if possible, but he came around soon enough.
And that's when he said you had to come in 1st for ten weeks straight.
Not exactly.
After I come in 1st for ten weeks in a row, I then have ten weeks to wrap the story up and end it.
That's the condition I gave.
The Chief Editor accepted it.
What happens if you don't come in 1st for ten weeks in a row?
Then I can't end the series.
It wouldn't be cool if another manga got first place.
Should that happen, I would try again to come in 1st for ten consecutive weeks. Then, I'd end my manga.
If I can't do that, I have to keep drawing the series until it gets canceled.
Getting canceled or staying in first place...
Such extremes.
Excuse me.
If this don't concern Natural, I'm leaving.
She hasn't changed.
Niizuma
Should you continue drawing a popular manga just because it's popular,
or should you end it when you want to?
It's a difficult question.
I can understand wanting to end it in the best way that you can.
But it'll hurt Shounen Jack if Crow ends.
The anime still ongoing.
If it was me, I wouldn't end my manga while it's still popular.
It'd be such a waste!
I think you should continue while it's still popular.
Are you serious?!
Niizuma already has all the money he could ever need!
He should end his manga now and just enjoy himself!
Work is just meant to earn you
enough money to live on, anyway!
Hiramaru, that's not what we're talking about here.
Right.
Well, even if you end Crow, you've still got Natural.
But Akina writes Natural.
I'd like to do another manga of my own one day.
I'm not against you ending Crow the way you want.
But I don't want you to end it this way, either.
I feel the same.
You're the artist we've always looked up to.
I know how you feel,
and excuse me for saying this, but I don't want you to end it now.
I won't let you!
Yeah.
We've always wanted to surpass him.
I don't want things to end without us ever having succeeded!
Yeah.
I see. If he ended it now, it'd be
like he quit while he was ahead.
Which means,
if we don't want him to end it, we need to overtake him!
That's correct.
So sorry, but Crow ain't ending!
Because I'm gonna pass you!
You can't.
No, we can!
Right, Saikou?
Yeah!
I understand how Fukuda and Ashirogi feel.
Even if I'm not against Niizuma ending it as he wants to,
as his rival, I want to surpass him.
We all can agree on that.
Yeah, I want to surpass Crow too.
I want to pass him and prevent him from ending it.
It'd be awesome if I were able to do it.
What are you talking about?
Crow is at the height of its climax! You can't win!
I didn't throw out manuscript after
manuscript only to lose to the likes of you guys!
Now you've said it, Master Niizuma.
Coming here has gotten us fired up.
I'll take you on!
I won't let you end your manga in such a cool way!
Yeah! Never!
How interesting.
Forget five weeks.
If anyone manages to beat me even once before I finish my final manuscript,
I won't end Crow!
He won't end it if we beat him!
We have eight more weeks... No, seven!
It's a challenge!
You're on!
ro...
Why, I wonder?
Whenever I am close to fulfilling my goals, all effort becomes fruitless
We walk ahead, hold each other, and with little things
we support each other to reach what we promised
When we lack confidence, we put a hand to our heart
and reread the pages we assembled into a story
They lead up to today and continue into the morrow
We will always be ourselves
tto...
until the day that our dreams come true
Next Time
Preview
I accepted Master Niizuma's challenge!
I'm pumped!
I want to get first place with Hiramaru.
Next time: Front and Center.
Front and
Center
I'll win and achieve my dream!