AAA
Takahama
I got my serialization! I couldn't have done it without your help!
AAA
Takahama
We just heard the news from Hattori.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
We can finally compete against each other with our serializations!
My first order of business is to beat you!
He just declared war on us.
First Fukuda, and now Takahama.
Things keep getting more and more interesting.
We need to work hard so that we don't lose!
Yeah!
Natural is 4th in the final ranking!
It didn't change.
Damn.
6th isn't good enough!
ano ne moshimo ima sugu ni kimi no moto he to
Hey, if I could go to where you are right now
ikeru naraba kono koe ga nakunattemo ii ya
then I could accept losing my voice
mezasu basho ga amari ni mo tooku
The goals I've set myself seem impossible to reach,
boku wa mou michi ni mayoisou da
and I feel lost on my path
kowareta jishaku wo ate ni shiteru n da
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in another's shadow
dareka no kage ni kakurete sa
nanika wo te ni ireru tame nanika wo tebanasu nante koto wo
If we keep letting go of some things in order to find something else,
tsuzukete mo kitto bokura wa otona ni wa narenai
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
narenai
Never
Every Night and Unite
All right. I'll be there to pick up the manuscript in a bit.
Let's have the meeting for GIRI there too.
Man, this feels great!
We're already preparing for our next
serialization and Kiyoshi hasn't even ended yet!
Speaking of, did you manage to find an assistant who can draw motorbikes?
Nope, not yet.
When it comes to motorcycle drag racing, I guess you could say that I drag my feet!
Um, Yuujirou...
Hattori's been acting a little strange.
He said that 6th place isn't good enough for PCP.
But 6th place is pretty good.
PCP is a special case.
How is it a special case?
It's one of those "unspoken agreements."
PCP is really getting responses.
I can't just let it get canceled...
Are you listening to me?!
Oh, sorry.
Please take this more seriously!
I absolutely cannot afford to lose to Ashirogi Mutou!
It'll be fine.
Within six months, PCP will probably be...
6th place isn't good enough.
If PCP isn't on equal footing with Crow and Natural within the next six months...
it'll be canceled.
What?
Those were the conditions.
It's not that surprising, is it?
When we ended Tanto...
We'll beat Niizuma Eiji.
So please let us end Tanto!
Oh, that's right!
I kept quiet about it because I didn't want to put more pressure on you.
But if we leave things as they are,
PCP will be canceled.
Natural's anime begins in April.
Fukuda and the others' new
serializations will enter the picture too.
Sounds like it'll be tough.
We'll have to be competitive against Eiji and Iwase despite all that.
We need to at least get to 3rd place.
PCP will end?
It's off the record, but it's true.
That kind of condition isn't right!
The harder I try, the more Takagi has to...
Doesn't this work to your advantage?
You wanted to beat PCP, didn't you?
Akina...
Do you actually enjoy competing with Takagi?
Does it make you happy?
O-Of course not!
It's important for Takagi be there so that I can be above him!
Well, there's no need to worry about them ranking higher than Natural.
What do you mean?
I just came from Niizuma's place, and...
Then Ashirogi's manga will be canceled.
So you feel the same way, huh?
Yes.
I don't think we'll lose against PCP as it is now.
When it comes to manga, Niizuma is always right.
Hattori even says he's psychic.
Niizuma said, "As it is now," right?
Yeah.
Call Takagi, and then give me the phone!
Huh?!
Do it now!
O-Okay!
We can't keep going on like this.
We have to find some way to kick it up a notch.
Excuse me for a minute.
Miura Gorou
Miura?
This is Iwase.
Iwase?!
Why are you...
I need to apologize.
I planned on using every trick in the book to beat you two.
However,
I've decided that this approach is ridiculous.
From now on, we'll compete fair and square, using only our manga!
Do you understand me? You two can't beat us as you are now!
H-Hold on! I'm not following you at all.
Niizuma said it himself.
He doesn't see PCP as a challenge as it is now.
Eiji did?
Think! Scheme! Use everything you've got!
If you lose to me like this,
you'll have nothing to blame but your lack of talent!
Understand?!
Iwase...
I understand.
You're exactly right.
Now that you've gone ahead and said all that...
we'll have to beat you!
I'd like to see you try.
Eiji and Iwase...
We've got some good rivals.
Yeah!
I'm taking a break! Nothing you say can stop me, Yoshida-shi!
Oh? What if I said that I'd cancel your tea date with Aoki?
Tea?!
Y-You finally set up the tea party with Aoki?!
Of course I did!
And it'll be here.
Yoshida-shi!
All you need to do is sign this.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Pledge Regarding Tea Party
Hiramaru Kazuya (henceforth known as Person A)
and Yoshida Kouji (henceforth known as Person B)
will sign this pledge regarding Person A's manga
Otter no.11 in accordance with the following terms.
Yoshida-shi, why are we having tea here?
Don't you want to show off your
unusually large and chic living room?
Oh, luxury apartments!
Aren't you glad that you took out that huge loan?
Yeah.
You should probably finish your manuscript before the tea date.
Now that you have something to look forward to, you won't take a break from Otter, right?
Right!
Yes!
That should last us another six months.
PCP - Perfect Crime Party
Popular series! Ashirogi Mutou
So he doesn't think he'll lose against PCP as it is now?
Right.
So PCP would stand a chance if we made changes to it.
Is that how we should interpret it?
Yeah.
That may have been the entire reason Niizuma phrased it that way.
By the way, you said that PCP is more popular with readers below the age of 10 and above the age of 18, right?
Basically, in a day they
would do 5-6 m. If they couldn't manage it,
they'd do 10 m the next day.
The only day they rested was the 16th.
The entrance was
made narrow enough to not
be found,
but you can walk inside upright.
In other words, a 108/65m
tunnel, huh.
It took six
years?
In my opinion, it's a hit with kids, and it
reminds adults of their childhood dreams.
It doesn't seem to be doing well among middle and high school readers.
Why don't we make the Party's actions more flashy then?
That's fine, but you have to make sure they're grounded in reality.
Crow
Wow!
Don't deviate from things that are possible in normal, everyday life.
Crow
Wow!
You're right.
This isn't a battle manga, so we have to limit ourselves.
Even if we don't have our answer right now, there's still six months left.
By the time the Obon special issue is released, we need to be on an equal footing with Niizuma's manga.
Exactly.
Damn it!
Even though I get what Eiji is saying...
I'll just have to read and analyze every popular manga we have from cover to cover!
March
Sun
Mon
Tues
Tues
Manuscript UP
8th Chapter
7th Chapter
Mashiro, we're running low on #62 gradient tone.
Already?
Well, I am applying it the way you instructed me to.
If you don't realize just how much that uses up...
All right. I'll order some more.
May I say something?
As someone who went to design school,
I believe you're relying too much on screentone.
Overusing it will actually result in a lack of depth.
U-Um...
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
A woman alone in a man's room.
That's quite risky, you know.
Your claim that we can't lose to PCP the way it is now piqued my interest.
That's right. We can't lose.
PCP is too plain.
Plain?
I suppose you're right. Its story is plain compared to that of a battle manga.
No, not the story. I was talking about the art.
The art?
Hey...
Don't you think PCP is a bit dark?
Are you doing too much inking and screentoning?
I didn't mean it like... Well, I might be, but...
I don't think it feels like a shounen manga.
The premise alone makes it different.
That's our unique characteristic.
No. It's a shounen manga, so I need to lighten it up.
In all of the popular manga up
until now, even the realistic ones,
there were parts where the style
became lighter and more refreshing.
PCP's story is realistic, so the art should be too.
But it's still a manga.
I can't just draw everything realistically!
I have to put in plenty of expressions that you can only find in manga!
Sometimes artistic! Flashy!
Stylish!
Like this! Do you understand?
That's enough, Niizuma.
I didn't come here to ask you what Ashirogi Mutou lacks.
Huh? You didn't?
I came here to ask you not to tell them.
Since you seem to be fond of them for some reason.
Because I'm their fan!
Regardless, I'd appreciate it if you didn't give them any advice.
Of course, even if you did, I doubt we'd lo—
I understand! I don't want to lose, either!
Let's make +Natural even more popular than it is now!
You're talented, so I know you have what it takes!
I-I'm talented?
Yes!
You're dropping out of college?!
I don't need a degree or a backup plan anymore.
What I need now is time to improve my art.
I already convinced my parents and texted Azuki about it.
I see.
We are serialized right now, after all.
This was one
heck of a hem stitch!
Then how about this stitched strap!
Saikou, I know you said you'd make changes gradually,
but chapter eight is already looking very different.
Really?
Chapters five and six are in 7th place.
Chapter seven is in 8th place.
We'll be in trouble if we lose any more ground to Niizuma.
I hope making the art lighter in chapter eight shows some results.
We're 5th in the final ranking?!
And by a close margin to Natural?!
It really went up!
So it really wasn't the story, but the art.
I'm still making changes through trial and error,
but if I keep this up...
The editorial department said that PCP's
improvement in this week's rankings must be a fluke.
Then the editorial department isn't paying enough attention to PCP.
We'll be in even more trouble by next week.
How so?
If this keeps up...
it won't only overtake Natural, but Crow too.
Ashirogi is changing their art style.
It's even better in their ninth chapter in this sample copy.
Is that why you did something different with the manuscript than what we discussed last week?
Yup. I redrew the whole thing after seeing PCP's eighth chapter.
But that'll let them overtake us even faster...
That won't happen.
The gap between us might close after
Ashirogi sees that manuscript, though.
Akina?
Is Miura not with you?
I came here alone today.
Zoom out here!
And pretend to...
Are these two...
This reminds me of when she asked Hattori what he thought of her as a woman.
She's not going after Niizuma now, is she?
Nah, I'm probably reading too much into this.
You seem to be taking your time with Crow.
Yes!
Will +Natural be okay?
What do you mean?
PCP won't overtake it in the rankings, right?
We'll probably lose to PCP's chapter nine in the immediate rankings when that issue goes on sale next week.
Niizuma Eiji is always right.
But +Natural's anime starts that Tuesday!
So we'll put up a fight in the final rankings!
Ashirogi is changing their art style bit by bit.
So Crow must go even higher than PCP!
I won't lose!
Damn! PCP overtook us!
The color illustration on the cover celebrating the start of the anime didn't do a thing.
Damn it!
PCP is in 4th,
just one place ahead of Natural in the immediate rankings.
But...
Watch out!
It's being born.
I-I hate to admit it, but this is good.
Yeah. The kids are sure to vote for this.
The anime that Azuki could've had a role in...
I have to make PCP an anime for her sake too!
+Natural!
Just as Niizuma predicted, we lost to PCP in the immediate rankings.
Let's make +Natural even more popular than it is now!
You're talented, so I know you have what it takes!
This country's clams really are delicious!
Hikaru Fishery's Clam Pack!
Promotional giveaway in collaboration with Otters 11!
Otters 11
Promotional campaign
collaboration
110,000 lucky winners will receive Otters 11 limited edition figures!
Clam
This is adorable!
Thank you, Hiramaru!
Isn't this great? You would go on about how you
wanted one every time that commercial came on.
It is!
Thank you so much.
Oh, this is nothing.
How does it taste? I bought that Earl Grey myself.
I'm sorry. I always drink Darjeeling, so my opinion on Earl Grey would be...
Darjeeling?
M-Yoshida-shi, can I speak to you in the other room?
Yamashita.
Yes?
You bastard! You told me that Aoki likes Earl Grey!
The aroma of Earl Grey is perfect for this chilly weather, don't you think?
I'm rather fond of Darjeeling, myself. I drank it pretty often back home.
That muscatel flavor is very nice.
You're quite knowledgeable.
Oh, not at all.
Niizuma, here's the sample copy of next week's issue of Jack.
Thanks!
Your art is amazing and all, but can you not do this again?
Roger!
By the way, Natural placed 4th in the final rankings.
After the anime started, it overtook PCP.
Did Miura already tell you?
Yes. It's just as I expected.
Akina again?
Probably.
Just how often has she been coming over?
Pretty much every day this week.
N-Niizuma!
The two of you are grown adults.
I don't mean to be crude, but please take it more slowly!
Please!
What are you talking about?
And I'll be a boy forever. That's why I draw shounen manga.
R-Right.
What?! Aren't they practically living together, then?!
Keep your voice down, idiot!
Sorry.
But Akina's doing this every night?
This is bad.
You're her editor.
Get over here and talk to her about this.
What? No way! She won't listen to a word I have to say when it comes to love.
Just get over here!
Yeah, they kind of give off that feeling...
Niizuma, did you tell them that I was trying to entice you?
I haven't said anything.
Here's the sample copy of issue 20 with chapter ten of PCP.
Thank you.
Take a look at Crow first.
Crow?
There isn't any dialogue!
He's telling the story with art alone!
After seeing PCP's eighth chapter, I heard that Eiji went back and completely redrew this chapter of Crow.
He realized that I was starting to change my art style.
He's saying, "Look at how well I can tell the story with art alone!
Can you do the same?"
I'm sure of it!
But can he stay popular like this?
He's certainly taking a risk.
Without any dialogue, the readers may feel something is lacking, and the number of votes may slightly decrease.
This is something he wanted to show me, even if it meant risking the loss of a few votes!
No way! The chapter without any dialogue got more votes?!
Yeah. I was surprised too.
Normally, it'd get less.
But when Niizuma did it, he managed to convince the readers that it was an amazing and novel idea.
Eiji's surpassed me in both art and votes now.
Natural, on the other hand, didn't advance like I thought it would. It's still in 4th place.
PCP came in at 5th by 9 votes.
9 votes?!
So close!
For the next three weeks, three new
serializations will start, one after the other.
Then during the following week in issue 26, PCP will get a full-color cover spread for its 15th chapter.
Full-color cover spread?
Really?!
We'll bet everything on that chapter!
Let's rank higher than Natural!
Right!
I'll write the best story I can for chapter 15 of issue 26!
And I'll draw something for the cover and title page that far surpasses anything I've done before!
What do you mean?
With mutual consent between Niizuma and Akina...
Could they be getting married?!
Niizuma and Akina?
It's hard to imagine, but maybe those with true talent are attracted to each other.
Should we tell them to stop?
I never said that.
Does Niizuma have a problem with it?
Honestly, I get the feeling that Akina forcefully persuaded him into it.
But after the fact, Niizuma seemed extremely excited about it.
I see.
Then there's no problem here.
Th-Thank you!
Takahama's new serialization is good!
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Yeah.
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
He managed to make a shounen
manga out of a courtroom setting.
All right, Road Racer GIRI!
1st place in the final rankings!
I'll keep on tearing through the competition!
Fukuda is amazing!
The energy in the second chapter is just as high as in the first!
And it really shows that Takahama's done his homework on courtrooms.
Seigi no Mikata
Seigi no Mikata's first chapter got 3rd place, and the second and third chapter were at 7th.
He's been right behind us the entire time.
Seigi no Mikata
Yeah, even though last week's new serialization dropped to 11th place with its second chapter.
Road Racer GIRI
I've been focusing on overtaking Natural in the issue with our front cover spot,
but it looks like we have Fukuda and Takahama to worry about too!
The manuscript with the cover spread has already been sent to the presses.
No amount of worrying will do us any good now.
You're right.
We've done what we can,
so let's focus on the manuscript we're doing now!
Hattori?
We've been had!
J-Just look at this!
The sample copy with our front cover spread?
Look at Natural!
What? This is supposed to be Natural, right?
Wh-What's...
Crow doing there?!
mogakinagara saikou no yume wo
The times when I fight and struggle and dream
katachi ni suru kono shunkan ga suki sa
of all the things I want in life is the best
tatakau you na te wo tsunagu you na
That's when I feel the bond between us and our strength to fight
kankaku ga shigekiteni da ne
Our view of the world overlaps and stimulates us
kousa shite
dakara motto migakou jibun rashiku arou
Let us polish ourselves, be more like how we should be
tsuzuita michi ni aru hazu
The future can be found on the path we walk
mirai wa
shinzuru mono ga chigau nakamatachi
My comrades believe in different things than me
Rival...and Friend!
butsukariau Pride
Our pride clashes
yuzurenai kore kara mo kokoro no mama susumou yo
I can't give up on it, I have to do what my heart commands me to do
junbi wa dekita
I'm ready
ikki ni kakeagaru tame no
I've got the unbending pride
akiramenai Pride
to run to the top now
hisshi nanda yo suki dakara suki wo mune ni susumu n da
This is my only choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
donna ashita ga matteru ka shiranai
I don't know what tomorrow will be like
asu mo
But I know that tomorrow, again,
bokura wa
girigiri
ganbatteru darou
we will do our best to get by
Next Time
Preview
If they don't try harder, PCP will be in trouble.
There's nothing to worry about.
Ashirogi always surpass my expectations.
I'll surpass myself!
Next time: Last and Password.
Last and
Password
Just keep thinking about it,
and you'll find the path that leads to your dreams!